Guide to the American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1899-2008.
American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records,
- Series VIII. Photographs and Slides
  - AHEAF Fellowship awardees, 1973-1974 (Box 214)
  - Board of Directors, 1971-1973; 2 folders (Box 214)
  - Morgue (Box 214)
  - Logo for Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 214)
  - AHEA Meeting, 1971-05 (Box 214)
  - Building artwork (Box 265)
  - Action art, October (Box 265)
  - Art, 1974 (Box 265)
  - Action art, 1971-1979 (Box 265)
  - Photos and art, August 1973 (Box 265)
  - Art for Action, 1975-1976 (Box 265)
  - Action art ballots, 1976 (Box 265)
  - Regional Meeting (Box 265)
  - Atmosphere (Box 265)
  - Ballot pictures, 1975 (Box 265)
  - Building sculpture (Box 265)
  - Business Home Economist of the Year, 1976 (Box 265)
  - Clothing - care labels (Box 265)
  - Congress (Box 265)
  - Contact sheets, 1958-1959 (Box 265)
  - Crafts exhibit [contains negatives], 1977 (Box 265)
  - Eastern Regional Meeting speakers and brochures, 1979 (Box 265)
  - Ecology [contains negatives] (Box 265)
  - Extension (Box 265)
  - Graphics, 1977-1978 (Box 265)
  - Handicapped children (Box 265)
  - 11th Lake Placid Conference (Box 265)
  - Miscellaneous dated files, 1975-1979 (Box 265)
  - Miscellaneous undated photos (Box 265)
  - NHEA Conference, 1978 (Box 265)
  - St. Louis (Box 265)
  - Washington (Box 265)
  - Miscellaneous material (Box 265)
  - Annual Meeting - Minneapolis, Chamber of Commerce Information, 1968 (Box 265)
  - Boston (Box 265)
  - Calendar Photos (Box 265)
  - FHA National Meeting - St. Louis, 1966 (Box 265)
  - Florida (Box 265)
  - Food and Nutrition (Box 265)
  - Group pictures from schools and institutes (Box 265)
  - Home Economists in Homemaking (Box 265)
  - Textiles and Clothing (Box 265)
  - Home Economists work in other countries (Box 265)
  - Home Equipment Management (Box 265)
  - Institution Management (Box 265)
  - Journal pictures, Chicago, 1965 (Box 265)
  - Group pictures (Box 265)
  - People in the News, November 1964 (Box 265)
  - San Francisco (Box 265)
  - Child Development (Box 265)
  - Journal photos, January 1965 (Box 265)
  - Dallas, Texas (Box 265)
  - Leadership Through AHEA slides, 2 folders (Box 265)
  - Leadership Through AHEA script (Box 265)
  - National Leaders Look at Home Economics slides (Box 265)
  - National Leaders Look at Home Economics script (Box 265)
  - Founders' View of the Future slides (Box 265)
  - Be Involved, Be a Home Economist [slides] (Box 265)
  - Be Involved, Be a Home Economist script (Box 265)
  - President Bates, report and slides, 1970-1971; 2 copies (Box 265)
  - Facts About A Very Important Profession slides and script, 2 copies (Box 265)
  - Young Home Economists on the Job slides and script (Box 265)
  - Home Economics - A Pacesetter Profession slides and script, 2 copies (Box 265)
  - Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 265)
  - AHEA Headquarter, slides, 1956 (Box 265)
  - AHEA building dedication slides, 1971 (Box 265)
  - How We Create an Image slides and script (Box 265)
  - Annual Meeting slides, 1979 (Box 265)
  - Building for the Future, slides, 1971 (Box 265)
  - Commentary for Family Life Abroad slides and program, 1963 (Box 265)
  - Your Time Is Now slides (Box 265)
  - This Is My Job and I Like It slides (Box 265)
  - Lake Placid ceremonies, 1964 (Box 265)
  - AHEA Annual Report slides, 1971-1972 (Box 265)
  - Field Service, 1966 (Box 265)
  - Field Service slides, 1974; 2 copies (Box 265)
  - AHEA staff, 1968 (Box 265)
  - Staff (Box 265)
  - Family Life Education slides (Box 265)
  - The Threatened American Family, Center for the Family (Box 265)
  - Center for the Family - Advisory Council meeting, 1973-05 (Box 265)
  - Ohio State, 1973-11; 2 copies (Box 265)
  - Home Economics in an Era of Concern (Box 265)
  - Action is Our Challenge (Box 265)
  - Pots and Pens - Home Economics-Communications Career Education slides (Box 265)
  - 50th Anniversary Dinner, 1959 (Box 265)
  - College Clubs, 1949 (Box 265)
  - Dr. Gladys Chalkley (Box 265)
  - Bureau of Human Nutrition Home Economics (Box 265)
  - Dedication and Headquarters interior slides and script, 1971 (Box 265)
  - Lake Placid-related Founders [contains negatives] (Box 294)
  - First annual meeting (Box 294)
  - AHEA past presidents (Box 294)
  - Friend of the Family Award-Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan [contains negatives] (294)
  - AHEA Members at American Institute of Baking, 1923 (Box 294)
  - Lake Placid meeting, 1973 (Box 294)
  - Glass slide prints (Box 294)
  - Cuban-American Home Economics Conference, Havana, Cuba, 26-28 December 1940 (Box 294)
  - Catherine Beecher and Mary Swartz Rose - reprints of publication photo (Box 294)
  - Home Economics history (Box 294)
  - Journal photos/art, Spring 1987 (Box 294)
  - Timeline feature (Box 294)
  - Peace Corps (Box 294)
  - Building 2010 Mass. Ave. N.W. - Construction, Grand Opening, Reception [contains negatives] (Box 294)
  - Headquarters' computer system (Box 294)
  - Headquarters, 1555 King St [contains negatives]. (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 294)
  - Washington D.C. (Box 294)
  - Betty Lamps [contains negatives] (Box 294)
  - Headquarters - stained glass panels (Box 294)
  - Headquarters [contains negatives] (Box 294)
  - Headquarters, 1600 20th Street N.W. Washington D.C. (Box 294)
  - Home Economists in Research (Box 294)
  - Wellness (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting and Exhibits, 1973 (Box 294)
  - Home Economists Extension/Research (Box 294)
  - AHEA ceremony for graduating seniors, 1952 (Box 294)
  - Aging, 2 folders (Box 294)
  - Selecting Foods - Adults and Children (Box 294)
  - Young Home Economist on the job (Box 294)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 294)
  - AHEA Members (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting Spread, Journal of Home Economics, September 1971 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting - Detroit [contains negatives], 1972; 2 folders (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting - Atlantic City, 1973 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting - Los Angeles, 1974 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting - San Antonio, 1975 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting speakers, 1975 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting - Boston, 1977 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 294)
  - Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 294)
  - Uniform for women enlisted in the Government's Food Conservation campaign (Box 294)
  - Planning meeting for AHEA annual meeting, 1947 (Box 294)
  - Meetings, Workshops, Seminars (Box 220)
  - International photos [contains negatives] (Box 220)
  - Peace Corps (Box 220)
  - Organization Leaders (Box 220)
  - Solar House (Box 220)
  - New York Stock Exchange (Box 220)
  - Students [contains negatives] (Box 220)
  - Elementary School Children (Box 220)
  - Textiles and Clothing (Box 220)
  - Women [contains negatives] (Box 220)
  - Vocational Education (Box 220)
  - Television (Box 220)
  - History (Box 220)
  - Weights and Measures (Box 220)
  - Staff [contains negatives] (Box 220)
  - Staff Recognition Ceremony [contains negatives] (Box 220)
  - FHA Tea, 1970 (Box 220)
  - Drexel University-International Workshop, July 1974 (Box 284)
  - March 1974 Photos [contains negatives] (Box 220)
  - Photos [contains negatives], 1974-04 (Box 220)
  - Teacher of the Year [contains negatives], 1975 (Box 220)
  - Teacher of the Year, 1976 (Box 220)
  - Recognition Ceremony, 1976 (Box 220)
  - Correspondence, microfilming archives (Box 220)
  - State Photo Descriptions (Box 220)
  - Annual Meeting Photos (Box 220)
  - Annual Meeting - Cleveland, Ohio, 1970 (Box 220)
  - Seattle Skyline (Box 220)
  - Founders' View of the Future (Box 220)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast Luncheon, 1954 (Box 220)
  - Pictures of Lake Placid era (Box 220)
  - Family Life Abroad Tours (Box 220)
  - Home Economists Helping Head Start: AHEA's Volunteer Nutrition Consultant Initiative (Box 220)
  - Library of Congress Family Life (Box 220)
  - College Chapters (Box 220)
  - Historic Child Development (Box 220)
  - Home Economics Early Extension (Box 220)
  - Current Home Economics Extension (Box 220)
  - Student Members, January 1969 (Box 220)
  - AHEA Members (Box 220)
  - A New Look at Home Economics Careers (Box 220)
  - Career strips, 1962 (Box 220)
  - Careers, 4 folders (Box 220)
  - Career shots (Box 220)
  - Nutrition, 3 folders (Box 220)
  - Group shots (Box 220)
  - Photo file - miscellaneous (Box 220)
  - Miscellaneous photos [contains negatives], 2 folders (Box 220)
  - Photos of early home economists, circa 1918 (Box 220)
  - A Visit to Our Home for Home Economics script, 1953 (Box 81)
  - Threads of Gold script, Indiana University, 1969 (Box 81)
  - America's Gifts to the Old World, 1916 (Box 81)
  - ...A Doing and A Becoming script, 1974 (Box 81)
  - Lake Placid audio visuals (Box 81)
  - AHEA - The Future of Home Economics script, 1973 (Box 81)
  - AHEA International Fellowships recipients, 1951-1952 (Box 81)
  - Baby Bathing with Hand Limitations Simplified slides and script, 1963 (Box 81)
  - Weaving slides, 1949 (Box 81)
  - University of Maryland (Box 81)
  - Leadership, 1968 (Box 81)
  - Leadership Through AHEA (Box 81)
  - Open House slides (Box 81)
  - Who's Responsible for Emma?, 2 copies (Box 81)
  - Benin: Xanoukpa Village Women, 1970 (Box 81)
  - Egypt: Dialogue, Instruction, Teacher Preparation [contains negatives] (Box 81)
  - Gambia: workshop, 1980-04 (Box 81)
  - Ghana: Family Planning Workshop, 1974-1976 (Box 81)
  - Ghana: Family Planning Workshop, 1974 (Box 284)
  - Guyana: large group photo (Box 81)
  - Jamaica: workshop photos [contains negatives], August 1979 (Box 81)
  - Korea: Workshops and Board meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 81)
  - Liberia: Family Planning discussion groups, 1976-02 (Box 81)
  - Panama Workshop and various other workshops, 1973 (Box 284)
  - Panama: Integral Health Program [contains negatives], December 1976 (Box 81)
  - Peru: United Nations Development Program Home Economics Experts, 1971 (Box 81)
  - Philippines: IFPP Pre-Congress Workshop [contains negatives], 1980 (Box 81)
  - Philippines: Self-Actualizing slides and script, November 1975 (Box 81)
  - Phillipines Workshop, 1975 (Box 284)
  - Senegal: Rural Vocational Training Program, 1968 (Box 81)
  - Sierra Leone: Workshop photos, 1973-1979 (Box 81)
  - Sierra Leone: Workshop photos, 1973-1979 (Box 284)
  - Ann Gilchrist Strong (Box 81)
  - Bangladesh: Functional Education and Community Leadership slides and script, 1976 (Box 81)
  - Taiwan: Family Planning Depth Training, 1973 (Box 81)
  - Thailand: Workshops, 1974-1977 (Box 81)
  - Thailand Family Planning Workshop, 1974 (Box 284)
  - Turkey: Family Planning Programs in Home Economics School, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Trinidad: Teacher Training and Workshop, 1975-1976 (Box 81)
  - Turkey:2nd Ad Hoc Advisory Committee (Box 284)
  - Zaire: Development of Primary Education in the Republic of the Congo, 1963 (Box 81)
  - Kenya: Kirathimo Model Village Family Planning (Box 81)
  - Clever Wives (Box 81)
  - Overseas, 1957-1969 (Box 81)
  - IFHE International Students, March 1970 (Box 81)
  - Penn State Workshop, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Home Economics in Other Countries (Box 81)
  - Nepal: 2nd Ad Hoc Advisory Committee (Box 81)
  - Nigeria: Journal of Home Economics photos, 1969-05 (Box 81)
  - Pakistan: Home Management Program, 1976-02 (Box 81)
  - Iowa State: Summer Institute, 1973 (Box 81)
  - International (Box 81)
  - Korean Red Cross Pamphlets (Box 81)
  - El Salvador, 1982-1983 (Box 81)
  - China Photos (Box 81)
  - Lesson Kit for Trainers of Adult Literacy Tutor (Box 81)
  - Inside My Mom, teaching guide (Box 81)
  - World Neighbors filmstrip scripts (Box 81)
  - Meeting the People (Box 81)
  - Eat to Grow (Box 81)
  - AHEA Message...New Building (Box 81)
  - Arlington School slides (Box 81)
  - Consumer Credit Workshop slides (Box 81)
  - 1600 20th Street slides - staff, interior shots (Box 81)
  - Publication photographs, 4 folders (Box 81)
  - Journal photographs, circa 1990 (Box 81)
  - AHEA Action photographs, July/August 1989 (Box 81)
  - Friend of the Family Award-Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan (Box 81)
  - International family planning slides (Box 136)
  - International miscellaneous (Box 136)
  - International workshop; family planning [?] (Box 136)
  - IWY Conference exhibit, 1975 (Box 136)
  - World Population Conference, Bucharest, 1974 (Box 136)
  - Agricultural education conference, Brazil, 1975 (Box 136)
  - Family planning newsletter images (Box 136)
  - International family planning (Box 136)
  - IFPP seminar, Jamaica, 1978 (Box 136)
  - Demonstration project, Cameroon (Box 136)
  - Working with Villagers, Philippines, 1982 (Box 136)
  - IFPP seminar, Philippines, 1980 (Box 136)
  - Sudan workshop, 1981 (Box 136)
  - Guatemala (Box 136)
  - Working with Villagers workshop, Panama; Home economics demonstration, Panama, 1981; 1976 (Box 136)
  - Family planning, India and Pakistan (Box 136)
  - Family planning, Ghana (Box 136)
  - Family planning/population education, Thailand (Box 136)
  - Family planning, Sierra Leone (Box 136)
  - Family planning, Nepal (Box 136)
  - Family planning, Korea (Box 136)
  - Workshop, Gambia, 1981 (Box 136)
  - International family planning (Box 136)
  - International family planning workshops (Box 136)
  - IFPP workshops/conferences, 2 folders (Box 136)
  - Working with Villagers workshop, Tanzania, 1981 (Box 136)
  - Family planning seminar workshop, Guatemala, 1981 (Box 136)
  - Family planning newsletter images (Box 136)
  - International family planning (Box 136)
  - Working with Villagers [?], circa 1980 (Box 136)
  - IFPP-related [?] activities (Box 136)
  - Family planning promotion workshop, Working with Villagers, 1979 (Box 136)
  - Teachers' Source Book workshop, Sierra Leone, 1980 (Box 136)
  - Miscellaneous international home economics/family planning (Box 136)
  - Family planning workshops/meetings, Asia, Africa and Central America (Box 136)
  - Home economics teaching workshop [?] (Box 136)
  - IFPP Ad Hoc Advisory Committee meeting, Turkey; family planning activities, Asia, Africa, 1974 (Box 136)
  - Family planning-Trinidad and Tobago, Ghana, Sierra Leone, FAO-IFHE meeting, Thailand, Philippines, Turkey, Panama (Box 136)
  - International Family Planning Project (Box 136)
  - Nepal and Trinidad, [photograph album] (Box 136)
  - Thailand, Korea, Philippines, Jamaica, [photograph album] (Box 136)
  - Taiwan, [2 photograph albums] (Box 136)
  - Various international slides, [binder] (Box 136)
  - Awards [contains negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 253)
  - TOY winners, 1997 (Box 253)
  - AAFCS Leaders Award, 1997 (Box 253)
  - New Achievers Award, 1997 (Box 253)
  - AHEA publications photos, circa 1940-1959 (Box 253)
  - Photos - Journal of Family and Consumer Sciences, November 1998 (Box 253)
  - Journal of Home Economics photos, 2 folders (Box 253)
  - Home Economics education [contains negatives] (Box 253)
  - Education [contains negatives], 1974-1977 (Box 253)
  - Children (Box 253)
  - International Home Economics (Box 253)
  - Ecology (U.S. Travel Service) (Box 253)
  - Black Home Economics [contains negatives] (Box 253)
  - Former AHEA presidents (Box 253)
  - Public Relations Depends on You (Box 253)
  - Board members, 1974-1975 (Box 253)
  - Board of Directors, 1975-1979; 4 folders (Box 253)
  - Board members, 1979-1980 (Box 253)
  - Dedication and interior of New AHEA Headquarters building [slides] (Box 253)
  - The Heritage of Home Economics: 1840-1920 [slides], 3 folders (Box 253)
  - Annual Meetings (Box 253)
  - Annual Meetings, prior to 1957 (Box 253)
  - Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 253)
  - 76th AHEA Annual Meeting, 2 folders (Box 253)
  - 79th Annual Meeting, Baltimore (Box 253)
  - Annual Meeting photos [contains negatives], circa 1980-1999 (Box 253)
  - Annual Meeting, Cincinnati, 1989 (Box 253)
  - Annual Meeting, contact sheets, 1991 (Box 253)
  - Annual Meeting, contact sheets, 1992 (Box 253)
  - 90th Annual Meeting (Box 253)
  - Annual Meeting, Seattle, 1999 (Box 253)
  - Annual Meeting, Chicago, 2000 (Box 253)
  - Old clippings (Box 253)
  - Old photos [contains negatives] (Box 253)
  - Assorted photos (Box 253)
  - Miscellaneous photos (Box 253)
  - 78th annual convention, ,1987 (Box 253)
  - Annual meeting, 2000; 2 folders (Box 253)
  - Annual meeting, 2001 (Box 253)
  - Children (Box 215)
  - Committees (Box 215)
  - Communication (Box 215)
  - Family economics-home management (Box 215)
  - Families (Box 215)
  - Family planning (Box 215)
  - Food and nutrition (Box 215)
  - Ganzin reception, 1972 (Box 215)
  - Home economists (Box 215)
  - Human services (Box 215)
  - Miscellaneous individuals (Box 215)
  - Home economics-activity shots, AHEA members, the profession (Box 215)
  - Institution administration (Box 215)
  - IFHE Congress, 1976 (Box 215)
  - Kitchen tools; Smithsonian Institution (Box 215)
  - Metric workshop, 1976 (Box 215)
  - Housing, furnishing and equipment (Box 215)
  - Miscellaneous photos on foam-core board (Box 215)
  - Annual meetings; Doris Hanson, circa 1970 (Box 215)
  - Historical images on foam core board (Box 215)
  - Stand for Children Day, AAFCS Board, 1996-06-01 (Box 215)
  - International groups and meetings (Box 215)
  - AHEA Headquarters dedication (Massachusetts Ave.) (Box 215)
  - Annual Meeting, Milwaukee, 1983; 4 folders (Box 215)
  - National Family Week celebration (Mildred Brooks, Emma King) (Box 215)
  - Blair, Clark, Halliday, Kyrk, Roberts, [Breck], Rock, Stevenson, Noble (Box 215)
  - Annual meeting, [1997?] (Box 215)
  - Unidentified individuals and groups (Box 215)
  - Barrier-free design (Box 215)
  - Presentation of Missouri AHEA anniversary proclamation, 1984 (Box 215)
  - French educators visiting AHEA Headquarters (Box 215)
  - David Jordan, Friend of the Family Award (Box 215)
  - Scottsdale meeting (?), 1993 (Box 215)
  - Bess Haley and Gail House (Box 215)
  - International Year of the Family (Box 215)
  - Staff party, August 1988 (Box 215)
  - Spirit Rising negatives (Box 215)
  - Miscellaneous negatives (Box 215)
  - 77th Annual Meeting (?) (Box 215)
  - Award presentations (Box 215)
  - Untitled (possibly Head Start nutrition program) [slides] (Box 2)
  - Headquarters dedication [slides] (Box 2)
  - You Can Do Family Laundry with Hand Limitations [slides] (Box 2)
  - Extending our Professional Dimensions [slides], 2 copies - 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Cook to Learn [slides], 2 copies (Box 2)
  - Founders' View of the Future [slides] (Box 2)
  - AHEA building dedication [slides] (Box 2)
  - Steam Cooking Equipment [slides] (Box 2)
  - Purchasing Canned Foods [slides] (Box 2)
  - Portion Control [slides] (Box 2)
  - Choosing Small Equipment [slides] (Box 2)
  - Through the Patients' Eyes [slides] (Box 2)
  - Vegetable Cookery [slides] (Box 2)
  - Planning Employee Jobs [slides] (Box 2)
  - Meat Purchasing, Parts 1-3 [slides] (Box 2)
  - Heritage of Home Economics 1840-1920 [slides], 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Heritage of Home Economics 1840-1920: script, bibliography and users' guide (Box 2)
  - Heritage of Home Economics 1840-1920, 3 cassette audiotapes (Box 2)
  - Heritage of Home Economics 1920-1985 [slides], 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Heritage of Home Economics 1920-1985: script, bibliography, and cassette audiotape (Box 2)
  - AHEA Annual Report 1971-1972 [slides] (Box 2)
  - The Culinary Hearts Kitchen Course-Sessions 1 and 2 [slides], 2 folders (Box 2)
  - AHEA Foundation awards [slides] (Box 2)
  - Home Economics in an Era of Concern [slides] (Box 2)
  - Former library and storage areas at AHEA Headquarters [slides] (Box 2)
  - Consumer Desk for Older Persons [slides] (Box 2)
  - Extra slides from Founders' View of the Future (?) [slides] (Box 2)
  - 11,000,000 Teens [slides] (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified (headquarters, annual meeting, Patterns of Progress?) [slides] (Box 2)
  - Your Times Is Now (#22-49) [slides] (Box 2)
  - AHEA Foundation presentation [slides] (Box 2)
  - Interior of AHEA building [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Annual Meeting (undated) [slides] (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified (Lake Placid, early home economics?) [slides] (Box 2)
  - Unidentified (headquarters, Lake Placid Club) [slides] (Box 2)
  - David Van Dommelen [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Bertha King [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Kathy Kurly (Kurley?) [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Sue Lahl [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Roberta Kahn [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Dr. Hanson, Betty Ruth Joyce, Maxine Westby, M. Reel [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - E. Fitzgerald [slides], circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Unidentified [slides], circa 1960 (Box 2)
  - Unidentified (headquarters, Foundation?) [slides], circa 1973 (Box 2)
  - Happy Home,, Seoul National University, IFPP (in Korean) [slides], 1979 (Box 2)
  - Janet and Janice at the [?] [slides], 1990-06-01 (Box 2)
  - Art prints: The Bath, Mary Cassatt; Girl with Balloon, Ruth Robbins; Desert Journey, Ruth Robbins (Box 163)
  - 2010 Massachusetts Avenue headquarters (Box 163)
  - Ellen H. Richards portrait (Box 163)
  - Alice Ravenhill (Box 163)
  - Mary Hemenway (Box 163)
  - Adelaide Nutting (Box 163)
  - Sir Michael Foster; group at Middletown; W.O. Atwater; Janet McKenzie Hill; women in kitchen; Dr. William Beaumont; group at Lake Placid; Catherine Beecher (Box 163)
  - AHEA staff and student workers, 1958 (Box 163)
  - Ninth International Congress photographs, 1958; 5 folders (Box 163)
  - 2010 Massachusetts Avenue headquarters (negatives) (Box 163)
  - Glass slides (box 1 of 2) (Box 69)
  - Glass slides (box 2 of 2) (Box 70)
  - Patterns of Progress, 1959; [glass slides] (Box 129)
  - International home economics education, [glass slides] (Box 130)
  - Slides on Headquarters (Victor Building 1600 20th St.; 2010 Massachusetts); Ellen Richards; Benjamin Andrews (Box 305)
  - Various slides on AHEA headquarters, activities and staff (includes Doris Hanson and Miss Swain; Carol Jamison; Rainey and McEnroe; Mrs. Spencer; Dale Evers) (Box 305)
  - Unidentified slides (possible subjects might be Home Economics careers, teaching children, cooking, shopping, welfare, institution administration), circa 1960-1970 (Box 306)
  - Slides showing images of life in Japan, [35mm slides and glass slides] (Box 306)
  - Images of families from other countries (Box 306)
  - Images of unidentified individuals [negatives] (Box 306)
  - Home Economics education (Box 215)
  - A Wheelchair Mother Prepares Formula (Box 215)
  - Margaret Morris; model of 2010 Massachusetts Avenue building, circa 1969 (Box 215)
  - Slides on AHEA activities, circa 1973 (Box 215)
  - Partners in Change multimedia presentation (Box 215)
  - AHEA activities, 1974-1975 (Box 215)
  - Recycling display, S. Hall, circa 1974 (Box 215)
  - Housing and interiors (Box 215)
  - Home Economists in Business, circa 1969 (Box 215)
  - Education [location not given] (cooking, food preparation, institutional management, etc.) (Box 215)
  - Adventure in Eating (D.C. Home Economics Association), circa 1967 (Box 215)
  - AHEA Membership Survey (presentation at Annual Meeting), 1979-06 (Box 215)
  - AHEA Foundation presentation (12 minute version) (Box 215)
  - 75th Anniversary; AHEA staff? (Box 215)
  - AHEA Headquarters dedication, 1970 (Box 215)
  - How the New Building Developed. (Salmon, Van Dommelen) (Box 215)
  - A Visit to Our Home for Home Economics (Box 215)
  - AHEA Annual Report slides, 1971-1972 (Box 215)
  - Be Involved, Be a Home Economist (Box 215)
  - Peace Corps; unidentified meeting (international?), 1968 (Box 215)
  - Ellen Richards; unidentified AHEA slides (Box 215)
  - Historical images used in "Here We Are" (Box 215)
  - Photo-Adelaide Steele Baylor, 1935 (Box 325)
  - W.O. Atwater, [glass slide] (Box 325)
  - Photo-President Eisenhower, Dr. Hazel Stiebeling, Ezra Taft Benson, Harris Ellsworth at the White House, 1959 (Box 325)
  - AHEA Gala (slides and negatives), October 1989 (Box 325)